It's 5.59 and I'm just waiting outside the shops for it to open.
Ta-da!
How I'm going to make the best baby lever under an hour and be at
work on time.
3, 2, 1, smile!
it's 5 59 and i'm just waiting outside the shops for it to open in
one minute because i've been craving these chocolate colored raspberries so bad since 2 a.m
this morning because i had a really bad migraine yesterday so i went to bed
in the middle of the day to sleep it off and work up like 12
hours later the next day at 2 a.m and since then i couldn't go back
to sleep and i still need to be at work in three hours, but it
will be okay.
I actually never bought these before myself.
I tried it a little bit from my friends and I fell in love since
then.
And I googled it and apparently it's like quite popular and hyped up anyway.
And I see the hype definitely.
Oh my god, I found them.
I'm so excited.
Okay, I'm going to get one of these.
And then one dark chocolate.
One...
Strawberries.
We've
got all the ingredients now because I'm going to do a bagel for
breakfast.
We're doing this all day.
Yes.
Okay.
It's like a vlog thing.
Oh okay yeah.
Oh that's one.
Looks like that.
Sorry I forgot to get something.
Can I go get that?
I'll leave this here for a second.
I'll
give you that as a back-up date.
Yeah, it is for small taxes.
Please tap or insert your payment card.
Thanks for shopping at Tesco.
Thank you, bye!
Yes, that's everything.
Some people don't get hungry at all in the morning and I'm the opposite of
that.
I wake up so hungry, right now I could eat the world.
I'm gonna eat those chocolate covered strawberries and bagels and have a huge breakfast before
work.
So I'm so excited right now.
I think if you're a morning person, most of the times you do wake up
hungry and like you need a breakfast in the morning?
I'm kind of annoyed that I forgot the salmon.
Oh shoot I forgot salmon.
oh no we're gonna have a vegetarian breakfast then shall we
oh do you know what i can't i can't compromise i've decided
to walk to the corn shop to get that salmon for my bagel because i
intended to have a feast this morning and I won't compromise.
Where's my phone?
And I still need to go to work.
How I'm going to make the best bagel ever under an hour and eat it
and be at work on time.
Of course we want to eat it up in crispy bagels so I'm going to
put it in the oven.
Ignore this.
I burnt my kitchen towel.
Mmm, this is going to be the yummiest bagel ever.
Honestly, you can't even find as good bagel as this outside.
Like, you would pay for this and actually pay double for this because that's how
good I make it.
Because whenever I make this bagel to my friends, they're like, I want more.
one tip that i learned from
social media i think which helps me a lot is if you can't finish your
avocado and you don't want it to go dark for next time you use it
what you do is get the other half the half that you're not going to
eat put it in a water like this and close it actually do you know
what i didn't learn this from social media my flatmate when i was in medical
school cat taught me this and it works.
Then put it in the fridge and it will be fresh and not dark.
Okay I'm getting warm.
I'm feeling the adrenaline for real because I'm tight on time.
So
we've cut our
veggies, squeeze some lemon.
Okay, we're also going to scramble some eggs.
I love them
extra cheesy.
We're gonna put lots of cheese on it.
and now I'm gonna
top it off with some salmon this
is
so fat do you see this
I've just finished seeing all my patients and now I'm gonna go straight to the
pharmacy or any shop to get some vitamin D tablets for myself because I saw
two patients in the last two days who presented with you know sleeping all the
time, feeling tired all the time, low concentration, basically all the symptoms that I have
a little bit.
So I'm thinking you know what do I have low vitamin D levels as well,
trying to take vitamin D as well.
This is actually such a common experience as doctors, like when you see your patients
having similar symptoms to what you have, you think, oh my god, I might have
this, I might have that, I might have cancer.
Or when I was a medical student, so many of my friends would read about
a disease and they would think, oh my god, I have this, I have that.
Do I have this disease?
It's just what happens basically.
But actually in the UK we're advised to take vitamin D tablets during autumn and
winter time regardless because of how less sunshine this country gets anyway, especially if you're
a minority like myself.
So like if you come from Mediterranean background or if you are African, Caribbean, Southeast
Asian...
like you're more likely to get low vitamin D levels.
Moral of the story, if you're in the UK or if you're in a country
that doesn't get a lot of sunshine, get yourself a over-the-counter vitamin D tablet and
take it daily.
Though this is not a medical advice, you shouldn't get medical advice on YouTube I'm
pretty sure.
I'm just talking about my experience and I'm gonna go get it now.
so
I'm
going to go get a drink.
I
got myself a monitor.
I never ever had a monitor in my life and never used one for my
personal work ever.
I've always had youtubers, entrepreneurs, gamers, anyone really using monitor and saying how it
improves their productivity and workflow so I wanted to give it a go and see
how having a larger screen helps
we've got cables they smell really weird
I think this is what the monitor sits on, right?
It looks like it.
I hope it's not too much building and gathering because I'm not up for that
right now because I just got back from my parents' house and I drove.
How do you do this?
Please don't tell me I need some tools for this or a screwdriver because I
cannot.
Oh, I don't think I do.
I bet this sits here.
Tada!
Okay, let's go.
Alright.
English.
Por favor.
What's happening?
English.
Oh no, not Chinese.
How do I go back?
What did I do?
Oh my god.
I'm
in my next door, named Diwali's.
We're with other doctors from the same hospital.
And then you layer it with the chana, put some pomegranate seeds on it, squeeze
a little bit of lemon, put some yoghurt.
Okay, I'll go behind.
I'm gonna sit here.
You better do it properly.
No, you're in the store.
Come a bit lower.
Okay, everyone look here.
3, 2, 1 Smile!
It's been 5 minutes.
Oh my god!
Next to the lens.
On the left.
Smile!
Shall we see if that was okay?
You guys can breathe it.
Oh my god that's cute!
Oh that's really cute!
That is so cute!
You can just take some onto it.
Should I turn this off?
Is someone going to record?
I can record.
Oh shit this is going to blow out.
Maybe I'll stay inside.
No there is a breeze.
Thank you.
Be careful.
What do you want to try more?
Once one person lights up the candle.
Oh!
The light!
Someone's just gonna light up the candle.
Come on.
Oh wow.
Oh there you go.
Look at that.
So pretty.
Happy Diwali!
Bye bye!